

Sherri Scheer

Web Developer/UX Design

sherrischeer@icloud.com 314.610.4882

Portfolio: sherrischeer.github.io/portfolio Website: www.sherrischeer.com

PROFILE

Hello! I am a self-motivated professional with experience in customer service and teamwork, who pays close attention to detail and making strong customer relationships. I have found my passion in the tech industry and would like to share it with others as well as utilize the skills I have obtained. I am very organized and detail-oriented. I love to learn and have a passion for accomplishment.

EDUCATION

LaunchCode Codergirl – User Experience (UX) Summer Cohort, 2018

St. Louis Community College – Web Development Certificate, 2018

Current Trends Academy - St. Peters, MO – Licensed as Cosmetologist, 2009

National Academy of Beauty Arts - St. Louis, MO – Nail Technician, 1999

University of MO St Louis –
BSBA – Bachelor of Science in Business
Administration, emphasis in Marketing, 1989

PROFESSIONAL SKILL

HTML5, CSS3 - websites and redesigns

JavaScript, jQuery – links, animations, timers, forms and data validation

UX/UI – went through the design process with Codergirl

Github, Bootstrap – my portfolio

Wordpress – my website

Photoshop – used on almost every project

Agile Methodology - studied this in Codergirl

PROJECTS

UX Design for WAF -- Class project at Codergirl, St. Louis, 2018

We used the Design Process for Women's Ambassadors Forum to identify conference attendees' and speakers' touch points and pain points with Empathy Mapping and Journey Mapping. Our feedback was obtained through surveys and interviews. We were able to offer the founder of WAF our Overview & Top Findings.

Troop313 Boyscout website re-design -- St. Louis Community College, 2018

I was assigned a website redesign in which I had to decipher through a lot of information and make a website. I researched typography and made wireframes for 3 pages. These are coded in Html, CSS and JavaScript.

EXPERIENCE

Hairstyles by Sherri & Changes Salon & Spa, St. Louis, MO – 1999-present My passion is to help people. I get to do this every day by helping them be beautiful and provide an easy way to maintain it. I build and maintain customer relationships by listening, customizing care and helping clients choose the best for their hair.

Administrative Assistant, Vineyard Christian Fellowship; St Louis, MO — 1994-1999 Accounting and Creative Team (bulletins, brochures, booklets, database, tax records)

Marketing Manager, Ocean Club; Southern CA — 1992-1994 Booked Banquets, created marketing ads, flyers, menus, etc. Created and managed nightly promotions.

INTERESTS

I believe if you want to give more, you have to become more. That is why I believe in having fun and routine. My interests include family, fitness, reading, travel, and movie night. I serve at church in the coffee-bar and on the Summit High School lacrosse board as Co-President in training.